# **Brett Burdick**

Web Developer – UI/UX

Atlanta, Georgia burdickbrett@outlook.com (770) 870-0668 brettburdick.com github.com/brett-b linkedin.com/in/brettdb

# **Recent Projects**

# Brew.place

08.2016

A responsive single page application where users can research beer throughout local breweries, as wells as bookmark their favorite beer into local storage. Using the AngularJS framework together with Bootstrap, allows for a clean layout, accessible on any device.

The most challenging hurdled with this project was working with an API that was not CORS compliant. Future goals will be to implement a proxy server to request JSON more effectively.

### Python RPG

10.2016

A text adventure RPG compiled completely from Python to run in the terminal. Included are fundamental concepts of the language like dictionaries, classes, and lists. Built with the subprocess, random and time modules to enhance user experience. Coding this was very enjoyable for me due largely in part that the debugging was simplified with explicit error messages and the OOP approach was similar to other scripting languages in my skillset.

#### Education

# Immersive Full-Stack Web Development ALP – DigitalCrafts (Atlanta Campus)

2016 – present

Dedicated over 665 classroom-hours covering both client-side and server-side web development. Spanning 16 continuous weeks, the curriculum detailed HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like AngularJS and jQuery. Server based technology training was based around both the LAMP stack and MEAN stack. Academics were constantly reinforced with daily exercises and ongoing projects that instilled the importance of agile development and stressed the importance of version control and continuous integration.

UI/UX design elective brought together the methodologies of research with industry design tools such as Sketch, Photoshop, and InVision to get a project from a wireframe to working prototype.

### Computer Networking/Cryptography/Switching Systems – Community College of the Air Force

2000 - 2001

1171 hours of training with certification in:

- Electronic Principles E3AQR2E231
- Data Processor/Display System Maintenance J4ASF2E2X1-037
- Computer Networking and Switching Systems E3ABR2E231

#### **Work Experience**

#### Server - Chops Lobster Bar - Atlanta, Georgia - (404) 262-2675

2015 – present

Delivered first-class customer service working in a high-volume premier steakhouse.

#### Corporate Training Manager - Ray's Restaurants - Sandy Springs, Georgia - (770) 955-1187

2008 - 2015

Created and implemented a web-based training course on <u>Schoox</u> to be used company-wide (05.2014). Managed a training team of 20 people to ensure protocol was met at every facet throughout new hire training.

# Computer Specialist – 552<sup>nd</sup> CRS/AWACS/MSIMS – Tinker AFB, OK

2000 - 2003

Performed maintenance on three E-3 mission simulators to support Airborne Warning and Control System mission crew training. Troubleshot and repaired faulty data display systems, saving valuable man hours and an estimated \$385,000 (07.2002).

- VETERAN OF OPERATION ENDURING FREEDOM
- RECIPIENT OF AIR FORCE ACHIEVEMENT MEDAL